Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. Newsletter Collection, 1910-2005 RL.00733
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Emotional Quality in Advertisements. [Author: Lewis, Edith] 1923 Apr.
End of the Era of Humbug. [Author: Anderson, Harriet] 1923 July
Exhibition of Home Furnishings. [Author: Unattributed] 1922 Oct.
Fallacy of Salesman Research. [Author: Cherington, Paul T.] 1930 Apr.
Familiar Human Material Doing a New Job. [Author: O'Shea, Monica B.] 1929 Oct.
Farmer's Dollar and How It Is Spent. [Author: Ashby, Bruce] 1927 Jan.
Few Facts About Our Work Abroad. [Author: Meek, Samuel] 1928 Nov.
Finding the Peak of Drawing Power. [Author: Freyd, Max] 1923 Aug.
Fordized Distribution. [Author: Unattributed] 1927 May
Foreign Trade of U,S, Shows a Substantial Increase. [Author: Unattributed] 1925 Oct.
Fruit of the Loom Decision. [Author: Unattributed] 1922 Aug.
Full Dinner Pail Idea Kept the Republicans in for Sixteen Years. [Author: Kinney, Gilbert] 1924 Oct.
General Motors Around the World. [Author: Tipper, Harry] 1928 Mar.
General Practitioner to Stay But Will Have to Work With Research Laboratories. [Author: Unattributed] 1925 Sept.
Gentle Reader. [Author: Leffingwell, Albert] 1922 May
Getting Advertising Produced. [Author: Kohl, Howard] 1922 Apr.
Getting the Most Out of Color. [Author: Johnson, Peirce] 1922 June
Give a Thought to Spain. [Author: Hartzell, A.E.] 1928 Mar.
Great American Cupboard. [Author: Walker, David N.] 1923 Nov.
Growth of Canadian Magazines. [Author: Unattributed] 1923 Aug.
Growth of Chain Drug Stores. [Author: Unattributed] 1922 June
Gruen Watches. [Advertisement] 1923 Jan.
Harlan Smith Comes to J. Walter Thompson Company. [Author: Unattributed] 1922 Sept.
Harvard Advertising Awards. [Author: Unattributed] 1925 Mar.
Headlines! Did You Ever Write a Good One?. [Author: Casseres, Aminta] 1922 Dec.
Headquarters of Some of the J. Walter Thompson Foreign Offices. [Author: Unattributed] 1928 Mar.
Housewives Write the Copy. [Author: Holmes, Mildred] 1923 May
How a Rubber Mat Revolutionized a Nation's Footwear Habits. [Author: Unattributed] 1922 Aug.
How Do Current Changes in the Field of Distribution Affect the Practice of Advertising?. [Author: Resor, Stanley] 1925 Dec.
How I Selected an Advertising Agency (Scott). [Author: McCabe, Thomas B.] 1929 Oct.
How Important are Store Demonstrations and Special Commissions to Clerks?. [Author: Resor, Stanley] 1923 Mar.
How Important is the Style of the Copy?. [Author: Casseres, Aminta] 1923 July
How Many Consumers Are Necessary for the Support of a Store?. [Author: Unattributed] 1925 Jan.
How Many Homes Does Magazine Advertising Reach?. [Author: Unattributed] 1925 Jan.
How Should the Advertiser Measure the Value of a Business Paper?. [Author: Mehren, Edward J.] 1925 July
How Strong Are the Chain Drug Stores in the Larger Cities?. [Author: Unattributed] 1926 July
How Strong Are the Chain Groceries in the Leading Cities. [Author: Unattributed] 1926 June
How to Get a Good Consumer Image. [Author: Maule, Frances] 1922 Mar.
How to Get Prestige for American Products. [Author: Kinney, Gilbert] 1926 June
How to Sell Salesmen on Advertising. [Author: Kinney, Gilbert] 1922 June
I Spend Half My Life in the Kitchen. [Author: Unattributed] 1925 Jan.
I Want a.... [Author: Cherington, Paul T.] 1922 Nov.
Importance of Investigation to an Agency and Its Clients. [Author: Mims, Stewart L.] 1922 June
Improvement in British Conditions. [Author: Paradise, S.H.] 1922 Oct.
Increase in Population Will Demand Cheaper Food. [Author: Unattributed] 1922 Nov.
Index of the Incomes of Factory Workers. [Author: Berridge, William] 1924 Mar.
International Trade as a Promoter of Peace. [Author: Lewander, Gosta M.] 1930 May
Introduction [to issue on advertising abroad]. [Author: Resor, Stanley] 1928 July
Invention--The Essence of Advertising. [Author: Waldo, Ruth] 1929 Dec.
Is the Chain Store Still In Its Infancy?. [Author: Unattributed] 1925 July
Is the Cost of Distribution Too High?. [Author: Mazur, Paul M.] 1925 Dec.
It Takes Too Much Time to Sell Bulk Goods. [Author: Acland, Peregrine] 1925 Sept.
J. Walter Thompson Company's Prize Essay Contest. [Advertisement] 1922 Aug.
J. Walter Thompson Prize Essay Contest. [Author: Unattributed] 1924 Mar.
J. Walter Thompson Radio Programs. [Author: Unattributed] 1930 Apr.
J. Walter Thompson, 1847-1928. [Author: Unattributed,] 1928 Nov.
Just a Piece of Key Copy. [Author: Watson, John B.] 1929 Aug.
Just What Effect Does Weather Have on Retail Sales?. [Author: Unattributed] 1927 Mar.
Keds Shoes (U.S. Rubber Co.). [Advertisement] 1922 Sept.
Keeping Peace With Mass Production. [Author: Unattributed] 1925 Jan.
Largest National Expense: How Advertising Helps Reduce it. [Author: Webb, Ewing T.] 1922 Mar.
Lo: The Cliff Dweller. [Author: Cherington, Paul T.] 1927 Sept.
Logic of the Department Store Organization. [Author: Mazur, Paul M.] 1925 Sept.
London-Paris Air Line. [Author: Paradise, S.H.] 1922 Feb.
Loyalties in the Making. [Author: Kinney, Gilbert] 1923 Jan.
Lux Flakes for dishwashing. [Advertisement] 1922 Oct.; 1923 Mar..
Magazine Circulations Among Industrial Employees. [Author: Unattributed] 1926 Jan.
Major Difficulties in Asia Minor. [Author: Miner, Henry J.] 1928 July
Make a Sale Every Time You Get an Interview. [Author: Acland, Peregrine] 1926 June
Management--The Third Ingredient. [Author: Unattributed] 1927 Feb.
Manhattan's Lunch Time Population. [Author: Unattributed] 1926 July
Manufacturer's Relations to Jobber's and Retailer's Salesmen. [Author: Cherington, Paul T.] 1923 Apr.
Mariemont [a planned community in Cincinatti]. [Author: Unattributed] 1926 Sept.
Market for Electricity and Electrical Devices. [Author: Unattributed] 1922 Nov.
Markets are People--Not Places. [Author: Watson, Clement H.] 1928 July
Mental Lunch Counters for Consumers. [Author: Boren, Wallace R.] 1930 May
Mid-Census Estimate Places Population of United States at 113,000,000 as of uly 1, 1925. [Author: Unattributed] 1926 June
Modern Advertising Methods in China. [Author: Hutchison, James L.] 1922 Aug.
More Automobiles Than Telephones. [Author: Unattributed] 1924 July
Mr. Groom Addresses Jewelers. [Author: Unattributed] 1922 Sept.
Mrs. Wilkins Reads the Ladies Home Journal. [Author: Townsend, Dorothy] 1923 June
Munsell Color System. [Author: Aymar, Gordon C.] 1922 Dec.
Nearly Thirteen Million Americans Live in Villages. [Author: Unattributed] 1926 Nov.
Net Profits of General Motors Double Ford's for 1926. [Author: Unattributed] 1927 May
New Era in the Automobile Industry. [Author: Kilbourn, Orrin P.] 1928 Nov.
New Evidence on Brand Consciousness. [Author: Unattributed] 1923 Apr.
New Factor in Social Development. [Author: Angell, Norman] 1928 Mar.
New Figures Supplementing Population and Its Distribution. [Author: Unattributed] 1924 Oct.
New Information. [Author: Resor, Stanley] 1924 July
New J. Walter Thompson Company Office on the Pacific Coast (San Francisco). [Author: Unattributed] 1923 July
New Organizations of Advertising Men. [Author: Unattributed] 1923 Aug.
New Practices in the Construction of Sales Quotas. [Author: Cherington, Paul T.] 1927 Jan.
New Types for Old?. [Author: Cunningham, Janet] 1929 Oct.
Note on the Increase of American Investments Abroad. [Author: Unattributed] 1925 Oct.
Now That The Excess Profits Tax Has Gone--?. [Author: Kinney, Gilbert] 1922 Apr.
Number of Domestic Servants in U,S, Decreases 350,000 in Ten Years. [Author: Unattributed] 1925 Sept.
Oh, But We Are Different. [Author: Paradise, S.H.] 1923 Nov.
On a Phase of Copy Style. [Author: O'Meara, Walter] 1924 Dec.
One Best Answer for Every Sales Resistance. [Author: Richey, S. Hunter] 1923 Feb.
O'Sullivan Heels. [Advertisement] 1922 July
Out-Britishing the Britisher. [Author: Unattributed,] 1928 Nov.
Outline of the New Book Retail Shopping Areas. [Author: Cherington, Paul T.] 1928 Mar.
Packages. [Author: Perkins, Frederick] 1922 Apr.
Paul T. Cherington Joins the Staff. [Author: Unattributed] 1922 May
Pebeco Tooth Paste. [Advertisement] 1923 Feb.
Pennsylvania Railroad. [Advertisement] 1927 Feb.
Personalities and the Public: Some Aspects of Testimonial Advertising. [Author: Resor, Stanley] 1929 Apr.
Personality and the Choice of Personnel (II): Can Psychology Help in the Selection of Personnel?. [Author: Watson, John B.] 1927 Apr.
Personality and the Choice of Personnel (II): The Behaviorist Looks at Personality. [Author: Watson, John B.] 1927 Mar.
Phenix Cheese Co.. [Advertisement] 1922 Nov.
Planned Prosperity. [Author: Klein, Julius] 1930 Apr.
Polling the Consumer. [Author: Watson, Richmond] 1930 May
Pool Versus the Chain Store. [Author: Unattributed] 1922 Nov.
Population and Its Distribution Helps the Government Solve a Problem. [Author: Unattributed] 1922 Feb.
Population Figures for Great Britain and Ireland. [Author: Unattributed] 1924 July
Practical Appeal in Advertising to Men. [Author: Leffingwell, Albert] 1924 Dec.
President Coolidge Sees in Advertising a Great Educational Force. [Author: Unattributed] 1927 Jan.
President of Large Insurance Company Endorses Dr. Watson's Plan. [Author: Unattributed] 1922 Feb.
Prestige and Good Will Protected by Sweeping Injunction. [Author: Unattributed] 1922 Apr.
Problem of Creating Desire. [Author: Woolf, James D.] 1922 Apr.
Purpose of the Essay Contest. [Author: Unattributed] 1922 Oct.
Radio Today is Not Just a Good-Will Medium. [Author: Casseres, Aminta] 1929 Oct.
Reader Advertisement. [Author: Kennedy, William D.] 1928 Nov.
Recent Distinguished Visitors to the New York Office. [Author: Unattributed] 1922 July
Reducing the Cost of Distribution. [Author: Hoover, Herbert] 1925 Feb.
Report on Visit to the United States of America. [Author: Willey and Locock] 1926 Apr.
Responsibilities of Modern Industry. [Author: Swope, Gerard] 1927 Jan.
Retail Shopping Areas Wins Book Award for Advertising Research. [Author: Unattributed] 1928 Mar.
Rice's Slices Bread. [Advertisement] 1929 Oct.
Richardson Roofing. [Advertisement] 1923 Mar.
Rose By Any Other Name. [Author: Cherington, Paul T.] 1922 Sept.
Sales and Advertising Problems of Merged Industries. [Author: Day, William L.] 1929 Mar.
Sanuel Reyburn Discusses Man-Power in Business. [Author: Fowler, George S.] 1927 Jan.
Savage Arms Corp. (rifles). [Advertisement] 1922 Oct.
Scientific Methods in Agency Work. [Author: Cherington, Paul T.] 1923 July
Second International Silk Exposition. [Author: Unattributed] 1923 Mar.
Securities Panic. [Author: Cherington, Paul T.] 1929 Dec.
Selective Distribution. [Author: Browne, Raymond] 1929 Mar.
Selling the Hospital Field. [Author: Unattributed] 1923 Apr.
Seventy Years of Growth. [Author: Unattributed] 1924 Nov.
She Wants It But She Doesn't Know It Yet. [Author: Ardery, Lois] 1924 Dec.
Shopping Center for Three Nations. [Author: Unattributed] 1927 May
Size of the Market for Heating Specialties Little Appreciated. [Author: Unattributed] 1923 Apr.
Snob Appeal. [Author: Maule, Frances] 1923 Mar.
Some Fundamental Principles of Organization. [Author: Cherington, Paul T.] 1927 Mar.
Some Grocery Chain Store Figures. [Author: Unattributed] 1924 Oct.
Some Lessons from Early New England Foreign Trading. [Author: Cherington, Paul T.] 1923 June
Some Marketing Problems of the Shoe Industry. [Author: Cherington, Paul T.] 1925 Feb.
Some New Developments in Commercial Statistics. [Author: Unattributed] 1925 Oct.
Some Recent Changes in the Rural and Small Town Market. [Author: Cherington, Paul T.] 1925 July
Some Recent Developments in Market Analysis. [Author: Cherington, Paul T.] 1927 May
Standard Color Scheme for Market Analysis Charts. [Author: Cherington, Paul T.] 1925 Oct.
State Labor Bureau Index as a Guide to Purchasing Power. [Author: Flinn, Richard A.] 1924 Mar.
Steady Increase in Purchasing Power of Consumer. [Author: Unattributed] 1925 Sept.
Study of Magazine Circulation in Cincinnati, Ohio. [Author: Unattributed] 1923 Oct.
Subject of the Essay Contest. [Author: Unattributed] 1922 Nov.
Sunbrite Cleanser (Swift & Co.). [Advertisement] 1923 Mar.
Swift's Ham and Bacon. [Advertisement] 1922 Dec.
The Advance Has Come Through Substituting Observation for Preconceptions & Passions. [Author: Unattributed] 1926 July
The Automobile Industry in Nearer Certainty Than at any Previous Time. [Author: Unattributed] 1927 Feb.
The Creative Plus Which No One Mind By Itself Could Achieve. [Author: Unattributed] 1926 Nov.
They Don't Want to Read It!. [Author: Rivers, Stuart] 1923 Feb.
Thinking as Viewed By the Behaviorists. [Author: Watson, John B.] 1927 Feb.
Timing Intensive Selling with Advertising. [Author: Richey, S. Hunter] 1922 Aug.
Transmuting and Delivering a Bowl of Cereal (Hot). [Author: Wengler, Harold] 1929 Aug.
Transplanting a New England Farm House to the Heart of New York City. [Author: Unattributed] 1922 Feb.
Trend in Outdoor Advertising. [Author: Thompson, Clyde S.] 1930 Apr.
Truth, Commerce, and World Peace. [Author: Henson, H. Hensley] 1924 Oct.
Two Examples. [Author: Stanton, Henry T.] 1922 Sept.
Under the Bushel? [making ideas graphic]. [Author: Unattributed] 1922 Feb.
Unusual Achievement in the Paint Industry. [Author: Posey, Chester A.] 1922 Aug.
Use of Dealer Electros in Merchandising. [Author: Groom, William S.] 1922 May
Using Waste Circulation to Sell the Product. [Author: Rothschild, Richard] 1922 Aug.
Value of a Window Display Not Wholly Dependent on Its Dignity. [Author: Unattributed] 1922 Dec.
Value of Recipes in Advertising. [Author: Hale, J. Mark] 1923 Aug.
Vanity Fair Silk Underwear. [Advertisement] 1922 Dec.
Vogue and Volume. [Author: Day, William L.] 1928 Nov.
We Are Still Laying Bricks Like the Babylonians. [Author: Unattributed] 1926 June
What About the Farm Market?. [Author: Ashby, Bruce] 1926 July
What Advertising Has Done for Type Design. [Author: Aymar, Gordon C.] 1923 June
What Cigarette Are You Smoking and Why?. [Author: Watson, John B.] 1922 July
What Do Our Rural Neighbors Buy? (Putnam Co., N.Y., and Randolph Co., Ind.). [Author: Unattributed] 1926 Mar.
What Do These Changes Mean?. [Author: Resor, Stanley] 1923 Dec.
What Does an Automobile Dealer Mean by Service?. [Author: Miller, George L.] 1922 May
What Does South America Offer the American Advertiser?. [Author: Ricketts, William] 1928 July
What Does the College Man Mean to Advertising?. [Author: Resor, Stanley] 1928 May
What is Fair?. [Author: Kinney, Gilbert] 1926 Sept.
What is Happening to the Thirteen Thousand Villages. [Author: Unattributed] 1927 Sept.
What Is the Trend in the Use of Color?. [Author: Dunne, Richard A.] 1925 July
What Makes Turnover and What it Means. [Author: Groom, William S.] 1923 Apr.
What Manner of Man--!. [Author: Kinney, Gilbert] 1923 May
What Price Progress?. [Author: Tomlinson, W.P.] 1927 Apr.
What the American Association of Advertising Agencies Does to Make Advertising Scientifically More Effective. [Author: Resor, Stanley] 1924 Dec.
What Will Follow the Rule of Thumb Era?. [Author: Aymar, Gordon C.] 1922 Aug.
What Will Your Business Policies Be in 1923?. [Author: Clark, Earle] 1923 Jan.
What Your Community Must Do Before Advertising. [Author: Resor, Stanley] 1925 Aug.
When Carmen Goes Shopping--. [Author: Hartzell, A.E.] 1928 July
When Sampling Increased Sales 30 Times. [Author: Unattributed] 1922 July
When the Chain Store Puts Its Wrong Foot Foremost. [Author: Fowler, George S.] 1926 Jan.
When Will Air Transportation Arrive?. [Author: Fuller, Edward] 1930 May
Where Are You Going--My Pretty Market?. [Author: Cherington, Paul T.] 1926 Nov.
Where the Urban and Rural Population Live. [Author: Cherington, Paul T.] 1924 Jan.
White Motor Trucks Utilize Irving Advertisement. [Author: Unattributed] 1922 Mar.
Who Does Not Seek After Persuasion?. [Author: Unattributed] 1925 Oct.
Why a Study of Purchasing Power is Important. [Author: Unattributed] 1924 Mar.
Why Is Your Copy So Long?. [Author: Leffingwell, Albert] 1922 Nov.
Why the Chain Store?. [Author: Gwinn, Ralph W.] 1929 Mar.
Will the Automobile Break Down International Boundaries?. [Author: Unattributed] 1927 Apr.
Woman Appeal. [Author: Maule, Frances] 1924 Jan.
Woodbury's Soap (Andrew Jergens Co.). [Advertisement] 1922 Dec.
Work of an Advertising Kitchen. [Author: Dodge, Astrid] 1922 Sept.
You Don't Know a Damn Thing About Raincoats. [Author: Anderson, Margaret] 1922 Mar.
Newsletters; Advertising agencies; Corporate culture; Consumer behavior; Advertising -- Research; Advertising agencies -- History; Marketing research; House organs; Brouillard Communications, Inc.; Dialog (Firm); J. Walter Thompson Company. Atlanta Office; J. Walter Thompson Company. New York Office; J. Walter Thompson Company. San Francisco Office; J. Walter Thompson Company; J. Walter Thompson Company. Chicago Office; J. Walter Thompson Company. Detroit Office; J. Walter Thompson Company. London Office; J. Walter Thompson Company. Los Angeles Office; Thompson Recruitment Advertising; Lord, Geller, Federico, Einstein; John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History
- Main Newsletter Series, 1910-2018
  Scope and Contents note
  The Main Newsletters Series comprises the primary house organ for the company, in all versions over time, from 1916 through 1986, when JWT became a unit of the WPP Group. The newsletter addressed issues of importance to the entire company, with articles on account news, client lists--or account gains and losses--and biographies and short notes on JWT staff, including professional accomplishments, promotions and transfers, visits to other JWT offices, and personal events (i.e. marriages, births, and deaths). The series also documents the results of both general and client-specific market research surveys, as well as general discussions of various markets and industries; television, radio, and print media developments (sometimes including listings of programs sponsored by JWT clients); and news from and profiles of JWT's offices and divisions around the world.
  There are some gaps in publication of these newsletters, most notably 1931-1945 and 1970-1975. Coverage of international affairs varies substantially, though all of the titles in this series provide some news from JWT's offices overseas. The richest sources of JWT international news are the newsletters of the 1970s and 1980s, when there is a substantial increase in the frequency and depth of attention paid to JWT operations globally. See also the International Newsletters Series. One particularly useful source is Thumbnail Sketches, a column published regularly in the newsletter from 1946 to 1964 which profiled JWT staff. Also common were reports on JWT advertising campaigns and their subsequent impact on both the market and the client; from 1946 until roughly 1962, the newsletters featured the Campaign of the Week, detailing particularly successful campaigns. A listing of Campaign of the Week topics appears at the end of the finding aid.
  The newsletters in this series were all published by the New York office, sometimes with local office newsletter inserts (see the Domestic Newsletters Series: Offices Subseries and the International Newsletter Series); copies of advertisements or management correspondence were sometimes attached as well.
  The newsletters are organized chronologically by the date range of publication. Folders containing correspondence relating to newsletters precede the listing of newsletter titles.
  Conditions Governing Access note
  Restrictions to access: Materials less than 15 years old are closed to non-JWT users. Where an item has been removed from containers and relocated, a dummy folder has been placed at the item's logical location within the container list, with the title enclosed by brackets and its physical location noted. In addition, bound and unbound originals of the 1922-1930 News Bulletin are closed to non-JWT users. Patrons may consult Use Copies that are available in the files.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Collection contains electronic records that must be requested through the collection guide and accessed in our reading room. Contact Research Services with questions.
  - Correspondence relating to newsletters, 1910-1976 and undated, 4 folders (Box MN1)
  - 1916-1922, News Bulletin
    Issued weekly 1916-1921, and approximately biweekly from 1922 on. No issues were published between numbers 55 (1917 July 9) and 56 (1918 July 8); numbers 69/70 (1918 Oct. 7/14) and 71 (1921 Mar. 15); and numbers 81 (1921 June 17) and 82 (1922 Jan. 9). Some issues include original JWT advertising and/or confidential letters attendant to these bulletins.
    - 1916 June 16-1922 Mar. 25, 15 folders (Box MN2)
  - 1922-1930, News Bulletin
    These booklet-size serial publications share a title with the earlier News Bulletin, but otherwise are different organs. They were published from 1922 to 1930 for external distribution, and contain articles by JWT personnel and outside contributors, primarily on topics of general interest to members of the advertising industry. Included are articles about consumer motivation, excerpts from market surveys, currentl client lists, and occasional JWT staff news. Originally issued monthly, beginning in February 1922, but publication became irregular, with no issue for September 1923, and varying numbers of issues for subsequent years. Issues are numbered sequentially (numbers 83-141) up to December 1929. In 1930, the publications's name changed to J. Walter Thompson Bulletin, with new numbering.
    - Bound originals (Closed to non-JWT researchers. See Use copies, Box MN5) (Box MN3)
    - Unbound originals (Closed to non-JWT researchers. See Use copies, Box MN5) (Box MN4)
    - Use copies, 1922-1930, 10 folders (Box MN5)
  - 1923-1931, Newsletter
    Published weekly 1923-1927, and biweekly from 1927 June-1929. Volume numbering begins 1928 Jan. 1 with Vol 10, no. 1. Published in one volume per year, while numbers ran continuously. Some issues include an index to previous issues.
    - 1923 Nov. 15-1925 May 7, 12 folders (Box MN6)
      Issue 72 not published.
    - 1925 May 14-1927 Feb. 17, 14 folders (Box MN7)
    - 1927 Feb. 24-1929 Dec. 15, 9 folders (Box MN8)
      Vol. 10, no. 3 (1928 Feb. 1) mislabeled as Vol. 10, no. 2; Vol. 10, no. 23 not published. Vo1. 11, no. 44 repeated (1929 Oct. 1 and Oct. 15).
  - [ 1930-1931, J.W.T. News: Removed to Oversize Newsletters, Box OV1] (Box MN8)
  - 1945, J. Walter Thompson Co. News Bulletin (Box MN9)
  - 1946, J.W.T. Weekly News (Box MN9)
  - 1946-1950, J.W.T. News, 8 folders (Box MN9)
  - 1951-1970, J. Walter Thompson Company News
    Published (more or less) weekly, 1951-1963 except biweekly in July and August, 1964-1970.
    - 1951 Jan. 1-1956 Dec. 31, 12 folders (Box MN10)
      Vol. 11, no. 48-53 (1956 Nov. 26-Dec. 31) mislabeled as Vol. 9, no. 48-53.
    - 1957 Jan. 7-1960 Dec. 28, 8 folders (Box MN11)
      Vol. 13, no. 34 (1958 Aug. 25) misdated as Sept. 1, 1958; Vol. 14, no. 19 (1959 May 13) mislabeled as Vol. 14, no. 18.
    - 1961 Jan. 11-1964 Mar. 27, 7 folders (Box MN12)
      Includes undated Christmas issues. Vol. 16, no. 19 (1961 May 17) mislabeled as Vol. 16, no. 18; Vol. 16, no. 20 (1961 May 25) mislabeled as Vol. 16, no. 19; and Vol. 16, no. 42 (1961 Oct. 25) misdated as Nov. 1, 1961; Vol. 17, no. 36 (1962 Sept. 7) mislabeled as Vol. 17, no. 37.
    - 1964 Apr. 3-1965 Dec. 30, 7 folders (Box MN13)
      Includes unnumbered Nov. 11 blackout issue.
    - 1966 Jan. 7-1967 Dec. 29, 6 folders (Box MN14)
      Vol. 21, no. 33 (1966 Oct. 7) mislabeled as Vol. 21, no. 32; Vol. 22, no. 25 probably not published.
    - 1968 Jan. 5-1970 June 2, 7 folders (Box MN15)
      Vol. 23, no. 21 (1968 June 14) mislabeled as Vol. 23, no. 20; Vol. 24, no. 18 repeated (1969 May 2 and May 9); Vol. 24, no. 28 (Aug. 8) missing all but pp.3-6.
  - 1957-1968, JWT News (Bound editions)
    - 1957-1962, 3 volumes (Box MN16)
    - 1963-1966, 4 volumes (Box MN17)
    - 1967-1968, 2 volumes (Box MN18)
  - 1975-1978, JWT News, 2 folders (Box MN19)